{
    "id": "37dc5f2730ce47f2addbbe137a0f0eb7",
    "title": "Degrees Of Comparison",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "James is as ………………… as his brother.",
            "description": "We use the positive adjective in the structure as ….as to say that people or things are similar.",
            "answers": [
                "tall",
                "taller",
                "tall than"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e47eeb32d41f4eb3a6511c06b38d9f7d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Alexander was one of ……………………. kings who ever lived.",
            "description": "We use the superlative to compare one person with the whole group that they belong to.",
            "answers": [
                "great",
                "the greatest",
                "the greater"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3c9ee3c8842f48189b278c18541a8141"
        },
        {
            "question": "Martin is …………………….. than any other boy in the class.",
            "description": "We use the comparative to compare one person with another person or persons.",
            "answers": [
                "more industrious",
                "the more industrious",
                "the most industrious"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "548c631cc27741fd8f7b27b36c15d184"
        },
        {
            "question": "Chennai is ……………………. than Mumbai.",
            "description": "Hotter is the comparative form of hot. We use the comparative to compare one person with another person or persons.",
            "answers": [
                "hot",
                "hotter",
                "hottest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a8ae00bc830143b8a641cc3b1fbeaf73"
        },
        {
            "question": "Very few cities in Asia are as ……………………. as Hong Kong.",
            "description": "We use the positive adjective in the structure as …as",
            "answers": [
                "big",
                "bigger",
                "biggest"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c326aa18ecbd40cb8e524c2798061bde"
        },
        {
            "question": "This cathedral is the ………………….. in South India.",
            "description": "We use the superlative to compare one person with the whole group that they belong to.",
            "answers": [
                "big",
                "bigger",
                "biggest"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d2af179653994eb289cd1cfb1744883d"
        },
        {
            "question": "An airplane flies …………………….. than birds.",
            "description": "Faster is the comparative form of fast.",
            "answers": [
                "more fast",
                "more faster",
                "faster"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5502ec043aff441d9b2367b29115984c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Kitchen appliances have made cooking …………………..",
            "description": "Easier is the comparative form of easy.",
            "answers": [
                "more easy",
                "more easier",
                "easier"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3b0b6647fd344f3a980468ec82e31b1d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Very few countries are as rich …………………… America.",
            "description": "The correct structure is as ... as..",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "as",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "035aee454e62491a9fbbd7849e3ae08e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Some beans are at least …………………….. as meat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more nutritious",
                "as nutritious",
                "nutritious"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4b6a41ba70034638861974e3f670c3c4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Naomi is ………………….. than her sister.",
            "description": "Less clever is the comparative form.",
            "answers": [
                "less clever",
                "less cleverer",
                "lesser clever"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c6e0f2e2103b46029f88b5d7bcec5058"
        },
        {
            "question": "Clara is …………………… than Sara.",
            "description": "Cleverer is the comparative form of clever.",
            "answers": [
                "more clever",
                "more cleverer",
                "cleverer"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "675855fee15b44f4a89e2c03e7802fed"
        }
    ]
}